

PROFILE

Seasoned and independent Front-End Developer with more than 1 year of experience in blending the art of design with skill of programming using HTML, CSS, JavaScript: plus, modem libraries and frameworks such as ReactJS, NextJS as well as NodeJS to building and maintaining responsive websites in the recruiting industry.

CONTACT

PHONE:

01997766489

LINKEDIN:

linkedin.com/in/habibur-rahman-06166b1b6

EMAIL:

mdhabiburrb@gmail.com

PORTFOLIO:

https://hr-bappy.github.io/Portfolio/

GITHUB:

https://github.com/HR-Bappy

ACTIVITIES AND INTERESTS

- Competitive programming
- Travelling
- Solving problem (math and IQ)
- Most importantly interested in learning more and new thing

HABIBUR RAHMAN

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

LinkedSage

February 2022 to Present

→ Designed and Implemented an interactive website LoanerBazar using ReactJs .

Jr. Front-End Developer

Shafa Care

March 2021 to January 2022

- →Designed telemedicine website ShafaCare and ShafaDev static website using NextIS.
- → Build web-based video calling system using agora.io with NextJS.
- → Developed ShafaCare admin dashboard using ReactJS

Jr. Front-End Developer + Intern

Halcyon

September 2020 to March 2021

- \rightarrow Designed and Implemented an interactive website <code>EnrichGrp</code> and <code>TalenTracker</code> using <code>ReactJs</code> .
- \rightarrow Utilized HTML, CSS, JavaScript to create 100+ responsive landing pages for both company and client using HTML CSS and JS according to PSD file.
- \rightarrow Responsible for maintaining website and deploy on the server.

EDUCATION

B. Sc. In CSE

International University of Business Agriculture and Technology 2017 to 2020 With CGPA: 3.73 out of 4

KEY SKILLS AND CHARACTERISTICS

Language:

C++ JAVA HTML CSS SCSS JavaScript

Libraries:

ReactJs React-Redux NextJs NodeJs

CI/CD:

Git

Project Management:

Trello

ACADAMIC PROJECT

- School Management System C, C++
- Ride Boat on a River OpenGL, C++
- Procurement Management System

Java, JavaFX, MySQL

- University Attendance System Java, JavaFX, MySQL
- School Management System Java, JavaFX, MySQL
- Weather <u>App</u>
 HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Portfolio
 HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- FootWear ReactJS
- Online Shopping and Trail ReactJS, MySOL
- Real Time Video and Text Chat App

Socket.io, NodeJS

ACHIEVEMENTS

Problem Solving

- → Solved more than 1000 problems in different online judge
- → Participate different Math IQ test

Competitive Programming

- → Attended 2 times NCPC in 2018 and 2020 Hosted by IUBAT and SUST
- → Participate more than 12 National and Inter University Programming Contest and got Certificate
- → Attend Google Hash Code Programming Contest in 2020

Course and Certificate

→ Completed many online and offline courses and got certificate

VOLUNTEERING

- → Mentor of intermediate and beginner session of IUBAT Programming club
- → Based on competitive programming arranged different seminar such as: weekly programming session, monthly programming contest.
- → Help students for academic courses and projects

REFERENCES

Dr. Utpal Kanti Das

Professor& Chairman, Department of CSE (IUBAT) Email: ukd@iubat.edu

Mohammad Sajid Shahria

Lecturer, Department of CSE (IUBAT) Email: sajid@iubat.edu

SIGNATURE



Habibur Rahman